fxdd.com 2014-11-26

# FXDD Privacy Policy | FXDD Forex Trading, FX Trade Solutions, Services

United States [](http://www.fxdd.com/us/en/)

  * /
  * /

  *   *   * 

We are committed to protecting our customers' personal and financial information. In the course of providing you with financial products and services, we need to collect and maintain certain nonpublic personal information about you. This Privacy Statement answers some questions about what nonpublic personal information we collect, what we do with it, and how we protect it. 

We do not sell your personal information to anyone. 

We collect nonpublic information about you from the following sources: 

>   * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms. 
>   * Information about your transactions with FXDirectDealer, LLC "FXDD". 
> 

We do not disclose any nonpublic information about you or former customers to anyone other than affiliates, except as permitted or required by law. For example, this may include providing information to companies that perform support services on our behalf or to providing tax information to the IRS. 

We restrict access to your nonpublic information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. 

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect nonpublic personal information. 

Should have any questions regarding your account, please contact the Compliance Department at telephone number (212) 791-6475. 

© 2014 FXDD

NFA #0397435 **MEMBER, NATIONAL FUTURES ASSOCIATION**

You may check FXDirectDealer, LLC's (FXDD's) registration and that of its Associated Persons by visiting the NFA's Background Affiliation Status Information Center (BASIC) at[www.nfa.futures.org](http://www.nfa.futures.org/). *During normal market conditions. The spreads are not fixed and may fluctuate with market volatility. [Click here](http://www.fxdd.com/us/en/forex-resources/forex-trading-tools/live-curency-quotes/) to see our spread chart.

FXDirectDealer, LLC ("FXDD") (CICI: 54930058T8RTMEHB3094) is currently seeking provisional registration as a swap dealer. [Read More](http://www.fxdd.com/us/en/forex-resources/faq/is-fxdd-a-registered-swap-dealer/)

**HIGH RISK WARNING:** Foreign exchange trading carries a high level of risk that may not be suitable for all investors. Leverage creates additional risk and loss exposure. Before you decide to trade foreign exchange, carefully consider your investment objectives, experience level, and risk tolerance. You could lose some or all of your initial investment; do not invest money that you cannot afford to lose. Educate yourself on the risks associated with foreign exchange trading, and seek advice from an independent financial or tax advisor if you have any questions.

**ADVISORY WARNING:** FXDD provides references and links to selected blogs and other sources of economic and market information as an educational service to its clients and prospects and does not endorse the opinions or recommendations of the blogs or other sources of information. Clients and prospects are advised to carefully consider the opinions and analysis offered in the blogs or other information sources in the context of the client or prospect's individual analysis and decision making. None of the blogs or other sources of information is to be considered as constituting a track record. Past performance is no guarantee of future results and FXDD specifically advises clients and prospects to carefully review all claims and representations made by advisors, bloggers, money managers and system vendors before investing any funds or opening an account with any Forex dealer. Any news, opinions, research, data, or other information contained within this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment or trading advice. FXDD expressly disclaims any liability for any lost principal or profits without limitation which may arise directly or indirectly from the use of or reliance on such information. As with all such advisory services, past results are never a guarantee of future results.
